Guide to the Tuol Sleng confessions and photographs, 1991-1993
Tuol Sleng confessions and photographs, 1991-1993
- Series IV. Confessions T-Y
  - Names: U
    - Uy Sambath, N/A (Reel 182, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/2/1977; 22/2/1977
    - Uy Sath, 3/3/1977 (Reel 180, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/3/79; 15/3/1978; 2/5/1978
    - Uy Thouren, N/A (Reel 182, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/2/79
    - Uy Yun, 25/2/1978 (Reel 181, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/4/1978
  - Names: V
    - Va Be, N/A (Reel 183, Frame 15)
    - Va Haill, N/A (Reel 184, Frame 12)
    - Va Ken, 4/1977 (Reel 184, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/5/1977; 5/5/1977
    - Va Sreng, 9/8/1976 (Reel 183, Frame 8)
    - Va Srorn, 1/8/1977 (Reel 183, Frame 19)
    - Va Thy, N/A (Reel 184, Frame 22)
    - Va Touch, N/A (Reel 184, Frame 9)
    - Va Voeun, N/A (Reel 184, Frame 13)
    - Vaing Ith, 18/12/1975 (Reel 183, Frame 23)
    - Val Sapon, N/A (Reel 184, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/8/1976; 8/9/1976; 10/9/1976; 18/9/1976; 20/9/1976; 26/9/1976; 28/9/1976; 1/10/1976; 2/10/1976; 3/10/1976; 4/10/1976; 5/10/1976(2)
      6/10/1976(4); 7/10/1976(5); 27/10/1976(2); 12/9/1976
    - Van, N/A (Reel 183, Frame 26)
      Dates of Confessions:
    - Van Doeurn, 27/1/1977 (Reel 185, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/3/1977; 8/3/1977; 2/3/1977; 4/3/1977; 7/3/1977; 6/3/1977; 1/3/1977; 27/2/1977; 29/2/1977
    - Van Noch, N/A (Reel 185, Frame 7)
    - Van Pech, 26/9/1977 (Reel 184, Frame 26)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/11/1977
    - Van Piny, 20/11/1977 (Reel 183, Frame 29)
    - Van Set, 1/1978 (Reel 184, Frame 23)
    - Van Sran, 3/1977 (Reel 183, Frame 14)
    - Van Tim, 25/5/1978 (Reel 183, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/5/1978; 30/5/1978
    - Van Vit, 7/1977 (Reel 183, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/8/1977; 24/9/1977
    - Vang Ke, 26/4/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 82)
    - Vann Chea, 8/12/1975 (Reel 183, Frame 24)
    - Vann Heang, N/A (Reel 184, Frame 15)
    - Vann Khatt, 27/12/1977 (Reel 184, Frame 5)
    - Vann Khom, N/A (Reel 184, Frame 8)
    - Vann Koeurn, N/A (Reel 183, Frame 18)
    - Vann Nang, 18/2/1978 (Reel 183, Frame 17)
    - Vann Nary, 10/5/1977 (Reel 184, Frame 7)
    - Vann Sang, 24/6/1977 (Reel 184, Frame 29)
    - Vao Hat, 17/10/1977 (Reel 184, Frame 21)
    - Var Lan, N/A (Reel 185, Frame 8)
    - Vat Nop, N/A (Reel 185, Frame 6)
      Nationality (if foreign): Unknown (Sdeng)
    - Ven Moek, 24/10/1977 (Reel 183, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/1/1978; 21/1/1978
    - Ven Ran, N/A (Reel 183, Frame 30)
    - Ven Van, 2/1978 (Reel 184, Frame 28)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/2/1978; 11/2/1978
    - Ven Vean, 18/6/1978 (Reel 184, Frame 27)
    - Ven Voeun, N/A (Reel 184, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: Month 10/1977
    - Veng Ho, 1/6/1978 (Reel 183, Frame 7)
    - Veng Ky, 30/5/1977 (Reel 183, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/7/1977; 19/7/1977; 16/10/1977
    - Veng Peng Kith, N/A (Reel 185, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/2/1977
    - Veng Song, N/A (Reel 183, Frame 20)
    - Veng Sophano, N/A (Reel 183, Frame 5)
    - Veng Taing Kin, 18/11/1978 (Reel 184, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/8/1978
    - Vicchai Amphanaan (Vichhat Amphanann), 21/12/1975 (Reel 185, Frame 40)
    - Vichhai, 6/9/1975 (Reel 185, Frame 41)
      Nationality (if foreign): Taing Island (Phoong Thai)
    - Vien Loeui, 19/10 78 (Reel 187, Frame 22)
    - Vieng Thanh Kvang (Kuang), 13/3/1978 (Reel 155, Frame 155)
    - Vieng Vann Chen, 16/3/1978 (Reel 187, Frame 23)
    - Vin Sophaon, 12/10/1976 (Reel 184, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/11/1976; 5/11/1976; 18/10/1976(2); 18/10/1976; 10/11/1976(2); 8/11/1976(4); 14/11/1976(2)
    - Vinh Minh, 3/1978 (Reel 187, Frame 24)
    - Vinh Minh (Hinh) Chau, 13/3/1978 (Reel 187, Frame 46)
    - Vinh Phy Long, 3/1978 (Reel 187, Frame 26)
    - Vinh Taeu Phoeung, 3/28/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 63)
      Sex: Unknown
      Age: Unknown
      Dates of Confessions: Vietnam
    - Vinh Thy Teak, 13/2/1977 (Reel 185, Frame 4)
    - Vinh Toeu (Toen) Phoeurng, 30/3/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 90)
    - Vit Taing, N/A (Reel 183, Frame 9)
    - Vith Peylam, 7/2/1976 (Reel 187, Frame 34)
    - Vo Dinh ( Pinh) Ngo, 2/1/1978 (Reel 187, Frame 51)
    - Vo Thy (Thi) Thvy, 28/378 (Reel 186, Frame 62)
    - Vo Van Oet, 9/5/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 95)
    - Vo Van Rom, 11/3/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 104)
    - Vo Van Thong, N/A (Reel 186, Frame 21)
    - Voek Somg, N/A (Reel 184, Frame 14)
    - Voek Van, 18/10/1977 (Reel 183, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 28/11/1977; 24/10/1977
    - Voeung Cheal, 5/10/1977 (Reel 184, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/9/1978; 27/1/1978
    - Voeung Eng, 1/2/1978 (Reel 184, Frame 24)
    - Voeurng Chhort, N/A (Reel 183, Frame 25)
    - Voeurng Ngoc Shen (Voeuing Ngoe Suân), 7/4/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 38)
    - Von Thong, 29/8/1978 (Reel 184, Frame 6)
    - Vong Heang, 25/10/1976 (Reel 184, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/3/1977; 12/3/1977
    - Vong Khim, 28/9/1977 (Reel 183, Frame 6)
    - Vong Loeung, 7/6/1976 (Reel 184, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/7/1976(6); 14/7/1976(3); 11/7/1976(2); 10/11/1976
    - Vong Mony, N/A (Reel 185, Frame 5)
      Nationality (if foreign): Kampuchea(?)
    - Vong Phan, 3/1977 (Reel 183, Frame 28)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/6/1976;v
    - Vong Sam Ath, 2/1978 (Reel 183, Frame 27)
    - Vong San, N/A (Reel 185, Frame 1)
    - Vong Sokha, 18/12/1975 (Reel 183, Frame 22)
    - Vong Troeurng (Troeng), 25/12/1978 (Reel 185, Frame 9)
    - Vor Nam Phong, 3/11/1978 (Reel 187, Frame 71)
    - Vor Um, 1/5/1978 (Reel 183, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/6/1978; 16/6/1978
    - Vork Van, 11/1977 (Reel 183, Frame 16)
    - Vou Hau Suc (Su’e), N/A (Reel 186, Frame 37)
    - Vung Vean, N/A (Reel 184, Frame 16)
    - Vunh (Vynh)Van Thai, 2/5/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 106)
    - Vy Sorn, N/A (Reel 184, Frame 1)
    - Vy Voeurt, N/A (Reel 184, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/11/1976; 22/11/1976
  - Names: Y
    - Y Chaam, N/A (Reel 165, Frame 18)
    - Y El, N/A (Reel 163, Frame 8)
    - Y Soup Ganthy, 29/9/1976 (Reel 166, Frame 28)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/9/1976(2); 28/9/1976(2); 29/8/1976; 2/10/1976; 5/10/1976; 20/10/1976; 30/10/1976; 1/1/1976
    - Ya Theang, N/A (Reel 161, Frame 9)
    - Yaan Yen, 13/1/1978 (Reel 164, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 31/1/1978
    - Yaang Koon, 21/11/1978 (Reel 165, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/12/1978; 20/12/1978
    - Yaang Phoeurng, 6/10/1976 (Reel 164, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/11/1976
    - Yaat Paong, 1/2/1978 (Reel 165, Frame 8)
    - Yal Yann, N/A (Reel 161, Frame 5)
    - Yan Pet Van, N/A (Reel 166, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/2/1977(2); 26/2/1977(2)
    - Yan Veth, N/A (Reel 160, Frame 9)
    - Yang Doep, 5/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 31)
    - Yang Mary, 24/1/1978 (Reel 163, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/2/1978; 1/4/1978; 7/3/1978
    - Yang Sim, 2/2/1977 (Reel 164, Frame 4)
    - Yanh Yin, N/A (Reel 161, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/11/1976; 18/11/1976(2); 19/11/1976; 20/11/1976(2); 31/11/1976
    - Yann Khy, 6/7/1977 (Reel 161, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/7/1977; 9/7/1977; 11/7/1977
    - Yann Kim Sun, 4/1/1976 (Reel 166, Frame 17)
    - Yann Kryn, 20/4/1977 (Reel 162, Frame 6)
    - Yann Moeurn, N/A (Reel 165, Frame 14)
    - Yao Bath, 11/1977 (Reel 166, Frame 9)
    - Yao Yoeuy, 4/7/1977 (Reel 160, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 15/7/1977(2); 23/7/1977; 20/8/1977
    - Yar Yaing Thong (Vo Van Thong), 8/4/1976 (Reel 186, Frame 20)
    - Yau Yeng, 7/1977 (Reel 166, Frame 14)
    - Yauk Chantha, 26/2/1978 (Reel 166, Frame 25)
    - Yauk Hom, 16/3/1977 (Reel 162, Frame 5)
    - Yauk Pann, N/A (Reel 166, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/5/1978
    - Yauk Thoeurn, N/A (Reel 164, Frame 10)
    - Yaun Cheav Ly, 12/8/1977 (Reel 164, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/8/1977; 15/9/1977; 16/9/1977; 6/10/1977; 22/11/1977
    - Yeam Palath, 1977 (Reel 166, Frame 24)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/3/1978; 14/2/1978
    - Yeat Soeurn, 30/1/1978 (Reel 165, Frame 9)
    - Yei Yann, 29/9/7 (Reel 164, Frame 24)
    - Yem My, N/A (Reel 162, Frame 15)
    - Yen Kun, 16/11/1977 (Reel 160, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/8/1977; 21/8/1977; 28/11/1977
    - Yeng Yoeurn, N/A (Reel 160, Frame 18)
    - Yi Hi, 14/2/1976 (Reel 162, Frame 3)
    - Yi Lach, N/A (Reel 165, Frame 3)
    - Yi Loth, N/A (Reel 160, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/3/1977; 4/4/1977; 27/6/1977
    - Yi Luy, N/A (Reel 162, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/5/1976 ( 2); 2/6/1976; 27/6/1976; 2/10/1976; 6/1976
    - Yi Man, N/A (Reel 164, Frame 13)
    - Yi Ngeav, 19/8/1977 (Reel 163, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/9/1977
    - Yi Saless Yasya, N/A (Reel 160, Frame 22)
    - Yi Samnath, 6/9/1975 (Reel 166, Frame 6)
    - Yi Sarun, 6/1976 (Reel 164, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/6/1976
    - Yi Siet, N/A (Reel 161, Frame 14)
    - Yi Than, 9/2/1978 (Reel 166, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/2/1978; 25/2/1978
    - Yi Yun, 27/6/1977 (Reel 160, Frame 21)
    - Yim Chan, 28/6/1977 (Reel 161, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/8/1977; 13/7/1977
    - Yim Chay, N/A (Reel 160, Frame 11)
    - Yim Chhoeurn, N/A (Reel 162, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/5/1976; 12/5/1976
    - Yim Chhoeurn, 15/2/1977 (Reel 165, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/3/1977; 15/3/1977
    - Yim Chhum, 1/10/1975 (Reel 162, Frame 10)
    - Yim Daim, N/A (Reel 165, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/1/1977(3); 12/1/1977(2)
    - Yim Dim, N/A (Reel 161, Frame 14)
    - Yim Heang Kaing, 11/6/1978 (Reel 166, Frame 10)
    - Yim Hoeurn, 4/2/1977 (Reel 162, Frame 11)
    - Yim Khait, N/A (Reel 165, Frame 12)
    - Yim Kim Yong, 3/1977 (Reel 164, Frame 8)
    - Yim Lamm, 3/8/1976 (Reel 161, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/9/1976(3); 23/9/1976; 22/9/1976(3); 24/9/1976; 26/9/1976; 27/9/1976
    - Yim Lonh, N/A (Reel 165, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/8/1976
    - Yim Lorn, N/A (Reel 160, Frame 24)
    - Yim Miin, 27/11/1978 (Reel 165, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/12/1978; 9/12/1978; 21/1278; 28/12/1978
    - Yim Nak, N/A (Reel 161, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/9/1976; 22/9/1976(3); 23/9/1976; 26/9/1976; 24/9/1976; 27/9/1976(2)
    - Yim Nim, 14/2/1978 (Reel 165, Frame 2)
    - Yim Oeurn, 19/9/1976 (Reel 162, Frame 2)
    - Yim Proeurng, 7/9/1976 (Reel 163, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/9/1976; 19/9/1976; 18//10/1976; 19/10/1976; 20/10/1976; 21/10/1976; 22/10/1976; 23/10/1976; 25/10/1976; 27/10/1976; 28/10/1976
    - Yim Sambatt, N/A (Reel 162, Frame 22)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/4/1976; 12/4/1976(12); 6/3/1976
    - Yim Saran, N/A (Reel 166, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/2/1976; 3/13/1976; 11/12/1978
    - Yim Sarin, 12/1/1976 (Reel 163, Frame 7)
    - Yim Saroeurn, N/A (Reel 165, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/5/1976; 19/5/1976
    - Yim Seng, 11/3/1977 (Reel 165, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/3/1977; 29/3/1977; 27/6/1977
    - Yim Simm, N/A (Reel 162, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/2/1977; 22/2/1977
    - Yim Soom Oll, N/A (Reel 166, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/11/1978(2); 18/11/1978; 11/1978; 2/12/1978; 9/12/1978(2); 19/11/1978
    - Yim Sun, N/A (Reel 161, Frame 11)
    - Yim Vin, N/A (Reel 161, Frame 17)
    - Yim Yean, 7/4/1978 (Reel 166, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/7/1978; 27/10/1978; 19/7/1978
    - Yim Yin, 30/10/1977 (Reel 163, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/10/1977; 2/11/1977
    - Yim Yon, 10/1977 (Reel 162, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/11/1977
    - Yim You Veing, 1/1/1976 (Reel 162, Frame 17)
    - Yim Youern, 19/7/1978 (Reel 164, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/8/1978
    - Yin, N/A (Reel 160, Frame 13)
    - Yin Dourng, 1/1979 (Reel 162, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/11/1978; 15/11/1978
    - Yin Ean, 23/7/1976 (Reel 166, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/8/1976(6); 3/8/1976(2); 4/8/1976(2); 5/8/1976; (6); 6/8/1976(3); 8/8/1976; 10/8/1976(4); 12/8/1976(4); 14/8/1976(2); 24/8/1976; 25/8/1976; 26/8/1976(2); 27/8/1976(7)
    - Yin Ean, 4/2/1977 (Reel 166, Frame 31)
    - Yin Heang, 13/3/1978 (Reel 187, Frame 63)
    - Yin Lo, 8/3/1978 (Reel 165, Frame 15)
    - Yin Lun, 13/4/1978 (Reel 166, Frame 3)
    - Yin Nath, N/A (Reel 162, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/11/1976; 4/11/1976; 8/11/1976; 13/11/1976; 16/11/1976; 19/11/1976; 20/11/1976; 24/11/1976; 6/10/1976; 14/10/1976
    - Yin Nuon, N/A (Reel 160, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/2/1977; 24/2/1977; 25/2/1977; 1/3/1977; 3/3/1977; 8/3/1977; 10/3/1977(2)
    - Yin Rian, 14/1/1978 (Reel 164, Frame 22)
    - Yin Rin, N/A (Reel 161, Frame 4)
    - Yin Say, N/A (Reel 162, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/10/1976
    - Yin Seng Heang, 22/2/1977 (Reel 162, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/3/1977; 4/3/1977(2)
    - Yin Soom, N/A (Reel 162, Frame 1)
    - Yin Sophanya, 9/8/1976 (Reel 160, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/1/1977; 3/1/1977(3); 6/1/1977; 28/12/1976; 31/12/1976
    - Yin Yim, 27/6/1978 (Reel 166, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/7/1978
    - Yin Yon, N/A (Reel 160, Frame 14)
    - Yin Youern, N/A (Reel 164, Frame 23)
    - Yiv Hout, N/A (Reel 164, Frame 20)
    - Yiv Srik, 20/7/1978 (Reel 166, Frame 30)
    - Yo Yoeurn, 26/6/1977 (Reel 163, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/1/1978; 14/5/1978
    - Yoeng Phonn, N/A (Reel 164, Frame 11)
    - Yoeu Kim Chhorn, N/A (Reel 161, Frame 2)
    - Yoeu Math, N/A (Reel 166, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/1977
    - Yoeunh (Yoeung ) Kao, N/A (Reel 186, Frame 29)
    - Yoeurn Yeuop, 30/1/1978 (Reel 166, Frame 5)
    - Yoeurng Chy, 5/1/1978 (Reel 162, Frame 9)
    - Yoeurng Keo, N/A (Reel 163, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/1/1978; 8/6/1978:
    - Yoeurng (Yoeung) Vann Liem, 28/3/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 61)
    - Yoeurng Yaing Hip, 14/3/1976 (Reel 187, Frame 30)
    - Yoeuy Nim, N/A (Reel 164, Frame 14)
    - Yok Meang, N/A (Reel 162, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/8/1976(4); 8/9/1976(2); 9/9/1976; 10/9/1976(3); 11/9/1976
    - Yong Chamroeun, 2/9/1977 (Reel 160, Frame 10)
    - Yong Chrorn, 20/2/1977 (Reel 161, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/3/1977; 12/3/1977; 29/3/1977; 1/4/1977; 27/4/1977
    - Yong Nuth, 6/1/1977 (Reel 161, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/2/1977; 8/2/1977; 11/2/1977; 13/2/1977; 23/2/1977; 25/3/1977; 21/9/1977
    - Yoon Ry, 5/1977 (Reel 162, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/9/1977; 11/10/1977
    - Yoon Soeurn, 28/10/1976 (Reel 163, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/3/1977; 4/3/1977; 7/3/1977; 18/3/1977; 19/4/1977; 30/4/1977; 9/6/1977; 5/11/1977; 22/11/1977; 5/12/1976; 9/12/1976(2); 12/12/1976
    - Yoon Yein, N/A (Reel 165, Frame 6)
    - Yoong Hoak, N/A (Reel 164, Frame 17)
    - Yoong Pauv, N/A (Reel 164, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/3/1976(2);21/3/1977; 31/3/1977; 9/4/1977; 12/4/1977; 24/4/1977; 2/5/1977; 17/5/1977
    - York Chuong, 9/12/1978 (Reel 166, Frame 26)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/12/1978; 10/12/1978; 23/12/1978
    - York Huor, 1/8/1977 (Reel 165, Frame 5)
    - York Moeurn, N/A (Reel 166, Frame 33)
    - York Song, 28/1/1978 (Reel 164, Frame 12)
    - Yorn Chhiem, N/A (Reel 161, Frame 16)
    - Yorp Yan, 19/9/1977 (Reel 166, Frame 29)
    - Yors Chhit, N/A (Reel 165, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/9/1976; 21/9/1976; 22/9/1976; 23/9/1976; 24/9/1976(2); 26/9/1976; 27/9/1976(2); 3/10/1976;6/10/1976; 7/10/1976; 12/10/1976; 14/10/1976; 15/10/1976; 17/10/1976
      19/10/1976; 22/10/1976; 8/11/1976; 15/11/1976
    - Yors Prim, N/A (Reel 161, Frame 18)
    - Yos Leng, N/A (Reel 164, Frame 19)
    - Yos Sambok, N/A (Reel 161, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/10/1976; 8/10/1976; 10/10/1976; 13/10/1976; 15/10/1976
    - Yos Soeurn, N/A (Reel 166, Frame 8)
    - Yos Sophann, N/A (Reel 166, Frame 27)
    - Yos Thoeurn, N/A (Reel 166, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/4/1977
    - You Eam, 25/2/1978 (Reel 161, Frame 10)
    - You Hak Chheng, 12/3/1977 (Reel 166, Frame 15)
    - You Ii, 17/1976 (Reel 164, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/7/1976; 27/7/1976; 28/7/1976; 29/7/1976; 30/7/1976; 31/7/1976(2); 3/8/1976(2); 5/8/1976(3); 8/8/1976; 24/8/1976(2); 29/8/1976(3); 1/11/1976; 1/11/1976
    - You Moeurn, N/A (Reel 160, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 15/10/1976; 17/10/1976; 27/10/1976; 28/10/1976; 30/10/1976; 8/11/1976(2); 3/11/1976; 4/11/1976(2); 24/11/1976(2); 3/11/1976; 5/11/1976(2); 6/11/1976(2)
      7/11/1976; 8/11/1976; 13/11/1976; 14/11/1976; 16/11/1976; 31/11/1976
    - You Peng Kry, 16/11/1977 (Reel 161, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/1/1978; 21/1/1978; 3/12/1977
    - You Phan, N/A (Reel 163, Frame 6)
    - You Phonn, 17/7/1978 (Reel 160, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/7/1978n
    - You Phos, 8/8/1977 (Reel 164, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/8/1977; 31/8/1977; 4/9/1977
    - You Sean, 28/6/1976 (Reel 163, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/7/1976; 9/7/1976(3); 14/7/1976(2); 10/7/1976(3); 21/7/1976(3); 12/7/1976(2); 13/7/1976(3); 16/7/1976(3); 17/7/1976(2); 18/7/1976(7); 19/7/1976(3)
      20/7/1976(3); 21/7/1976(5); 22/7/1976(4); 23/7/1976(5); 24/7/1976(4)
      31/7/1976; 28/7/1976; 26/7/1976: 27/7/1976(3); 28/7/1976(5); 29/7/1976(4)
    - You Thann, N/A (Reel 160, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/10/1976; 28/10/1976(2); 29/10/1976; 31/10/1976(2); 1/11/1976; 2/1/1976(2); 24/11/1976; 25/11/1976
    - You Thlang, 1/6/1978 (Reel 166, Frame 4)
    - You Tol, N/A (Reel 164, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/9/1976(2); 10/9/1976; 13/9/1976; 14/9/1976(2)
    - Youv Chhom, 14/7/1977 (Reel 162, Frame 23)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/8/1977; 31/8/1977
    - Ypuen, N/A (Reel 166, Frame 32)
    - Yun, N/A (Reel 162, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/4/1977; 13/2/1977
    - Yun Hor, 18/1/1976 (Reel 164, Frame 3)
    - Yun Ngath, N/A (Reel 166, Frame 22)
    - Yun Peng Seng, 17/6/1978 (Reel 163, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/7/1976
    - Yun Savuth, N/A (Reel 164, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/6/1976; 5/7/1976(2)
    - Yun Yann, 6/1975 (Reel 164, Frame 7)
    - Yuom Heang, 25/12/1976 (Reel 166, Frame 23)
    - Yuos Sok, 7/1976 (Reel 166, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/8/1976
    - Yuth Phong Sammran, 6/9/1975 (Reel 185, Frame 48)
    - Yuth Saroeun, N/A (Reel 160, Frame 23)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/6/1977; 22/7/1977; 29/7/1977
    - Yutt Choeuy, 14/1/1978 (Reel 165, Frame 4)
- Other Microfilm Reels
  - Materials in the cabinets, including Khmer Rouge periodicals (Reel 93-102; 112-115)
  - Charts (Reel 188)
  - Hu Nim and Takeo file plus other prison information outside of Tuol Sleng (Reel 198)
  - Retakes of defective reels (Reel 189-197; 199-213)
- Photograph Albums (black and white)
  - Three Ringed Binder of Prisoner Photographs (mug shots) (Box 1)
    Photo numbers 1-1000
  - Three Ringed Binder of Prisoner Photographs (mug shots) (Box 2)
    Photo numbers 1001-2000
  - Three Ringed Binder of Prisoner Photographs (mug shots) (Box 3)
    Photo numbers 2001-3000
  - Three Ringed Binder of Prisoner Photographs (mug shots) (Box 4)
    Photo numbers 3001-4000
  - Three Ringed Binder of Prisoner Photographs (mug shots) (Box 5)
    Photo numbers 4001-5190 (missing photo 5185)
    Mixed mug shot and full body shot